Hello,
Ethan. What's up, bro?
How you doing, Dude? How's it going?
Long time to see man.
Yeah, it's going good. It's going good.
I saw your message. Um, congrats on the,
uh, the performance there.
Thank you. What did you think to it?
Is that, that that was our first ad,
so we scripted that ourselves.
Amazing. Um, So do you remember Finn,
my business partner I spoke to about
That's amazing, dude.
Yeah, I mean, it's, it's a win, bro.
I think like you didn't script ads before this, right?
No, that was, that was, it was from your course we used
your, your structure. Oh,
F**k yeah. From the course.
Hell yeah, dude, that's amazing.
Um, well, yeah, there's, you know, when you,
when you script it, you have so much more control right?
Over the, the creative direction.
Um, and I see, like, I would love to see the ad,
if you don't mind sharing it, but, um,
Yeah, sure.
But is, I mean, as long as the client's happy, right?
Like they're getting results now, you're kind of, um,
going from just an editing service now to like,
almost creative strategy.
You know? I think that's, it's the way to go, um, with
where your business is at.
Um, then you can hold onto clients for a lot longer too.
This, this one was the first one we did.
So we're working with the media buyer for that company,
and he's give us quite a lot, a few improvements on it.
Um, so,
and the next ones are just being tested at the moment,
and we've not got the results back for them,
but I'll, I'll send you, I'll send you it now.
That's dope, man. Yeah.
How, how has it been working
with the media buyer from your experience?
Um, really not very good.
There's this, there's this other brand we're working with
as well, and the media buyers are quite lazy
and they just kind of chuck, chuck information at you.
Mm. And you have to properly decipher it.
It's quite a struggle. Do you, would you agree?
Yeah, I definitely, I've worked with amazing media buyers
who are so pinpoint accurate, detailed, like, who, like,
do the job for me,
and then I work with some who are like, um, you know,
you're like, what are you talking about?
Um, yeah.
So I think that's, that's the challenge with anybody.
You know, we're working with different team members from
different companies and such.
It's like you have to kind of prepare, you kind of have
to have your own methodology
or systems that you can, like,
at least if they're not in the right direction,
like you can have a system, a process of some sort.
Right. And I'm sure you'll learn that
as you work with more media buyers.
It's like, you want to kind of like take control
of the situation, uh, if they're not as organized
and detailed and stuff, right?
Yeah. That's a, yeah, that's, that's spot on.
I was, um, I was gonna make a, like a brief document
for the client to fill in so I I know what I need much more.
'cause Yeah, the information from them is really bad.
So I was gonna create like a template that they can fill in,
and so I know exactly what needs to be done.
Totally, man. 'cause all you need, right?
It's like you give me the information
so I could do a better job, right?
But if you're not giving me the right information, then I'm,
I'm, I'm still in the unknown here.
And, um, to be able to transfer that information.
So it's like, uh, for,
for you potentially, it's like, okay, well what are,
you know, what are those key metrics?
The ones that you sent spend cost per acquisition,
ROAS purchases, revenue stop rate, right?
Um, those are pretty much your key metrics.
Um, and I think in the very beginning stages,
um, it's really important to monitor that.
Like those early metrics when you first launch,
you know, 'cause sometimes like CTR
and CPC, like some
of those things will look really good on
the very, on the beginning.
And then they'll start to die out.
Like they won't, they won't translate into sales.
Um, so it needs to have best of both worlds.
It needs to have high CTR, but also profitability. Right?
And, um, and that's what we're really looking for.
So from the media buying perspective, like they're just not
to dog on any media buyers.
Like they're just, they're
just throwing it out there, right?
They're, they're hitting buttons
and they're like, all right, well, this one didn't work.
Turn that one off. Uh, this one looks kind of good.
All right, keep that one going.
And from a creative standpoint, it's like, whoa, okay.
Like we just, we just put a lot of work into that, you know,
to get there and say,
and then maybe they'll like,
I need like 10 more hooks or whatever.
And you're like, okay. Like, let's,
let's really think about this first
before we start requesting a bunch of things.
Um, is that what you're experiencing?
Yeah, exactly. And it must be difficult for you as well.
'cause you do the full production and everything.
So if you've spent like, uh, all your day filming
and then the media buyer just turns it off straight away,
that must be horrible.
I mean, yeah, it happens all the time.
Yeah, dude, it, that's why it's like, it's a, it's a very,
it can be very painful process.
It's very time consuming
to create content, you know, just in general.
And when you're running ads, it's like,
if it doesn't work, it doesn't work.
There's no, putting more money into a failing ad is never
going to make it better.
That's like one of the lessons I've learned in the past when
I was running my own, like dropshipping ads.
I used to think, oh, if I just spend more money on this ad,
the, the metrics will improve.
But that's not the case.
And you need to be, um, you're, you're, you'll,
you'll know right away, early metrics
if an ad shows promise.
So it's like first, you know, 50, a hundred, 200 bucks,
it's gonna really indicate whether it's a winner or a loser.
Um, some of the things that I look for for sure, like,
you know, obviously those CTR rates are big.
Um, you know, some of the brands I work with, like have,
you know, for me it's like, it's like an ego thing.
If I can, if I can score really high click-through rate,
um, for example, like yours, I don't see a click
through rate on the, um, but the stop rate is 30%, right?
That's like pretty good. You want like 30% or more?
Um, video of a slack. Sorry. Yeah, no worries. Yeah. Okay.
Sorry for interrupt. Oh yeah, no, you're good.
But like, if I get A-A-C-T-R of like, you know, three to,
or like four to five, 6% or something like that,
and the cost per click is like under a dollar.
Um, it's telling me that, you know, we are, we are
creating something compelling that's grabbing
attention and stopping the scroll.
You know, that's, that's like
we did our job on the editing side or the production side.
That's like key indicator for me. Okay.
Now are these translating into sales?
That's where it can get very mixed messages,
or you need to dig a little deeper as to how
to diagnose that issue.
Because if you're not making sales on it,
it could be two things or Yeah, number one, the main thing
is you're not converting them on the landing page.
So either the product page, actually, I'm gonna wait for,
uh, Eric to join.
'cause we're talking about some good stuff here.
We're talking about metrics. Um, so I'll hold off.
E Oh my god. Dude, that fricking
stash is sick, bro.
You look like a completely different person.
That's my, uh, second, um, what is it?
I don't know. Personality. My brother.
Oh, your alter ego. Alter ego.
I'm, I'm, wow, I I've always wanted to grow that,
but I can't get it to connect,
Dude. You
know, I wasn't able to, you know how I did it.
I just kept on trimming it.
Ah, because it goes sparse, right? It's like, right.
So I just had to keep on throwing it. Oh, looks cool.
Video editing and mustaches or add RX and mustache.
That's a topic for today.
I think so. I mean, I, I trim mine
'cause I look like a dirty person with it,
but, you know, I think,
I think I'm inspired by your mustache. Um,
What's up Ethan?
Dude, I, I'm actually stoked that you jumped on.
We were just in the middle of talking about metrics,
performance conversion, working with media buyers
and it sounds like you are currently doing that right now,
or you have been, right?
Yeah. But yeah. Yep. Yep.
Go ahead. And so we were talking about
how Ethan right now, he's um, he has his own, uh,
video editing agency
and he's taking on clients, um, doing performance ad edits.
And now he just started writing his own scripts based off
of the course, uh, ads or X course.
He took like the scripts that worked for us and applied it
and it worked for his business
or like the, the clients, which I think is a huge success.
Um, now the problem is working
with different media buyers from different types
of brands all have different levels
of experience and detail.
And so one of the problems he's experiencing right now is
working with people who, like, who just aren't as clear
as to like the information that Ethan's looking to extract
so that he can do a better job.
Um, but I was just talking about more so
when I'm launching creative
and I'm working with the media buyer, like what are the,
the key metrics that I'm looking for?
Right? I know you an you asked that question a a while back.
Yeah. Um, before I get into it, I was wondering if, if, um,
you had any updates on that?
No. End of the year it's all changing.
I'm asking for all that, but it
has to do on the end of the year.
'cause we do focus groups on it and just talking about it.
But those, uh, what is it?
I have it down the CPCs, CTRs, roas and all that.
Watch percentage. Mm-Hmm.
Not even in the, our, our spectrum. That's
Crazy. Yeah. That's insane,
dude.
What, what is it that you guys are looking for?
What they're looking at is cost per subs.
Cost per sub. Yeah. Period. Period.
Like, and then whoever has the most cost per sub is
basically we do like one to 10.
Right. First being the best.
So whoever has the most
cost per sub, um, wins.
Even if the cost per sub is like 80 bucks.
Really high. Yeah. Yeah.
When it's that high, they don't, it doesn't matter
because the sub is what, what they're looking at.
And I, I always like was saying like, that can't just be it.
'cause that sub, once it happens on the landing page,
I don't have any control of that landing page on sub.
Right. There is no way. Correct.
What I'm trying to do is get them through the door, right.
Or get them at the, the front of the door. Mm-Hmm.
And then there's no metrics on that.
So this starting January, those are the things
that are going to be in play.
Amazing, man. Yeah, that's exactly
what we were talking about is like those front-end metrics.
'cause that's what we have control over
as creatives, as editors.
And um, if an ad,
and I totally understand, you know, sub getting a sub,
you have them for, they probably have an X amount of months
that they're on or years 90 day retention.
Yeah. So they know that their numbers work out, you know,
even if it's unprofitable on the front end.
Right. Um, so I was telling Ethan that if, um,
you know, if your a's not converting,
but it's showing promise like high CTR, low CPC, you know,
high retention rate,
but it's not converting, um, it's not turning into sales.
You know, that's, that's a landing page issue
and that's an offer issue.
And those two things are very important.
So like your landing page,
if it's not converting could be like, it's too confusing,
it's not concise enough.
You're not promoting, uh, the top usps.
There's not enough social proof, right?
There's so many components to that's too complicated.
It's too simple. Um,
and then if your offer isn't dialed in,
and this is one of the hardest things I think
to test when you're a brand,
and that's not really within our wheelhouse or control,
but it's like, are you offering, you know, a, a gift?
Are you offering something for free?
Are you offering a bundle?
Are you offering something for a discount?
Are you offering a package?
Are you offering, you know what I mean?
Um, all those things are I think the brand's responsibility
to strategize and test.
Um, and I, it sounds like for you, obviously your brand is
so big, you know, they have their own strategy in place
and so they have a very clear offer.
But for some low, you know, brands
who are just starting out, like it may not be clear
what that is for them yet.
And, um, and so it takes some testing.
So I think from a creative standpoint,
it's like if your ads are getting them to the door,
you know, you, you have shown success.
Um, even if it's not converting, then it's now
it's a process of elimination of okay, where in the funnel
do we now course correct
or optimize if we know that we're getting cheap clicks?
'cause the cheaper the click,
the better your ad is grabbing attention.
Like, that's, that's like golden rule.
Um, the more expensive your clicks, like for example,
you can be in a very competitive niche, um, like lawyers
or like beauty or something.
And like if your ad's just like f*****g that good,
then it's gonna, it it's gonna be cheaper.
Um, now the watch time
and all that stuff, watch time, um, scroll, um,
what is it, the thumb stop rate.
All of these metrics are like ammunition for us to
further define where we can improve ourselves, um,
with our creative, with our messaging,
with our sequencing, right?
All of those things are gonna be our, our levers.
Um, and so a lot of the times
when I'm working on an ad
or with a media buyer, I was telling Ethan,
sometimes they give me like really amazing reports
of like, this is what worked.
This is what didn't, here's what we suggest we do.
And I'm like, yeah, I just go
into Premiere and I do my thing.
Um, and then there's times where it's like it's not working
and it's like, yeah, okay, well what,
like what do we change?
Yeah, yeah. What do we do? What do we do?
Um, you know,
and some, some business owners have like crazy a, DD
and like they don't know what they're focusing on.
So it's like you're not,
you're no longer just an editor at that point.
Sometimes you're like a psychologist.
Sometimes you're, you know, we're, you're dealing
with personalities, you know, different, um,
different workflows and stuff.
Um, but for example, like, um,
I, I always like to base off of winning.
Like I have to start from somewhere
where I know it's like proven.
You know, I don't know if that's your process,
but it's like, okay, if I'm just starting with a new brand
or I'm jumping into a, jumping into a, an account
or something, it's like, okay, well, you know,
from the last year or two, like
what has been the bus biggest success for us
and why, you know, so that becomes the analysis of like,
okay, that becomes my, my meat and potatoes
and then I build off of that.
'cause starting from, because like you can take a, a concept
and then like you can build off that, right?
Kind of replicate that success, copy it.
And then you can take something from another company
that's doing a different style that we haven't tested
and then put that into that winning structure.
Now you have a different combination of different styles
and angles, but within that same winning structure, that's,
um, that's how I like to do it.
Uh, at least when it comes down to like new brands.
But would love to hear any of your guys' insights
and like, learnings in the past couple weeks.
You know, I had something to on top of what you're saying,
it's still universal.
Everything's module. You could take that and put it on
because there's that formula that you always do
and you're not starting from scratch just editing
and designing something, right?
Or trying to, oh, let me tell a story here.
There's always that formula that you have. Mm-Hmm.
I think that's the best thing to have a reference point
of what's already winning
and take that into whatever industry it is.
Yeah, totally.
Uh, you had mentioned that Ethan, like, so what John had
told me to do is come up, you know,
ask him about CPS getting all that data.
Is that what you're also doing for your,
the new brands that you're working with?
Because they don't know what they want.
But then if you tell 'em like, I need these metrics
or KPIs and stuff like that.
So now they're able to get that to you.
Does that, does that help? Will that help you?
Um, what's CPS Cost per sale? Cost
Per subs or CPC cost per click. Sorry.
Okay. Um, you know, asking them, Hey,
can we have these metrics so I know
what exactly what I'm looking at?
'cause that's what John had told me, like,
you need these metrics so that, you know, going in,
you're actually looking something solid
and data on your end that you can use as an editor.
No, not, it wasn't exactly data related.
We didn't really get the results that, um,
the results I sent John were, they're from a board
that the media buyer and the client share together.
Mm. But he did, the media buyer did go over me on a call
and kind of went like frame by frame
and explained to me some of the things
that he thought could be better.
But at the moment we're just testing them iterations.
So hopefully you'll be able to get the results from them
and then compare and improve from there.
But I do, I dunno about you both,
but I much prefer working with like, actual data,
like having two videos side by side
and seeing one that does well and one that doesn't do well.
And you've got the data and you can see like if it's, um,
thumb stop, then you know
that the hook needs working on it rather than someone just
kind of eyeballing it and,
and just saying, I think that they know best.
Ah, yeah.
Have you ran into that John, like
where you had a client Right.
And they do a focus, like they're, Hey,
let's brainstorm why this video didn't work.
But all they're looking at is the front side rather
than behind the scenes.
Like the actual data behind it.
Yeah. Or do you just watch, oh, okay.
I know that, um, you know, that hook didn't work,
but you're looking at the actual video
and you're doing what Ethan, you know, what they're doing
going through the video one by one, like step
By step. Yeah.
You know, I think the, the hardest part is when,
when clients do this, like
before they even launch the video Mm-Hmm.
Because they'll spend so much time trying to perfect it.
Mm-Hmm. And it eats up weeks of just back
and forth revisions without even like putting it out.
Running it. Yeah.
And I'm like, bro, you like,
like these little changes aren't
gonna matter if it doesn't work.
You know, like we're gonna, if you don't
Put people behind it seeing it,
it's not gonna work. 'cause it's only them. Right?
Yeah. It's just they're them and their own egos external.
Yeah. Um, so that's always an issue.
I mean, when you're a service,
it's like you kind of have to do that.
Um, just especially
'cause our policy is like unlimited revisions,
but on the backend when you know you are going
through these creatives like step-by-step, um,
I think it it, you have to come from
a neutral place as best you can.
You know, I think the ego definitely wants to come in
and correct and defend or whatever.
And when you get a ton of people,
you get too many cooks in the kitchen,
I think is very dangerous as well.
I've had that before.
You know, people have super strong opinions
and they're just opinions.
And, um, as a creative, as an artist,
like you can't take that personally.
Um, I don't know. Does anybody get like that?
Like when they, when somebody's like critiquing their work?
Yeah. Yeah.
You're like, f**k, you're like,
you don't know what you're talking about.
Um, I get like that a hundred percent.
Um, I sometimes there's an opportunity to
present, you know, alternative options.
Um, 'cause sometimes the, the decisions aren't like
as sound because everyone is coming.
Like people who are typically revising videos, maybe,
maybe they have experience in editing on creative.
Maybe they don't, you know,
maybe they are just media buyers.
Sometimes you have to, you have to understand like
where their level of expertise comes from
and whether it's like justifiable as a,
as a, as a solid point.
Like, you know, I I think from certain,
certain people I'm like,
you don't know what you're talking about.
Like, like, so I'll if if that's the case, like I'll suggest
maybe we should try this instead.
Maybe we should try an easier solution.
Or I'll make an alternative version just to make you happy.
But I do believe that we should continue
with this test that out.
'cause everyone just has to kind
of like, learn for themselves.
Like, oh, that, that worked, that didn't work.
Like, we're always constantly testing hypothesis
as like people, you know, like that's really
what experience is.
It's like, let's try it.
If it doesn't work, then okay, let's not do that again.
Um, but yeah, it's a tough one. I think.
Um, especially when you're in those focus groups.
What is a focus group for you? Like what does that entail
For, for me?
Yeah. And your company. Yeah.
We'll run out bet's best performing ads for the week
and some ads can stay there for a few weeks.
But we're always looking at what ran that week,
Uhhuh, Right?
And so we're, we're looking at like sometimes tube
science or Sapphire.
They'll even have, we hired 'em out
and we're like, okay, they're on top today.
You know? And so why did this work?
And we're looking only on the front end.
Did you know, like, um, just scrolling through the video.
I see For me, I like, I wanna look at
where the drop rate was
and you know, where was the click through
and how much did they watch?
Yeah. But then I, it's not, it's not on the focus group
or it's not in that, um, brainstorming session.
I see Where it's at is I have to go into the ad ad, um,
ads manager or whatever TikTok is.
Right. And, and I'm looking at
and seeing where all the drop offs
and then I'll do comparisons and stuff like that for myself.
Yeah. But I think it's easier
and better if they understand where that
plays a big part on videos as well.
But they're not looking at that.
They're looking at like, oh, um, maybe it's,
it's the hook that didn't work.
Or maybe it's that middle part.
But I'm like, dude, if that hook never worked in general,
how are they gonna even watch the end of the, you know, end
of the video Or sometimes, you know,
this focus group they'll wanna do like, Hey,
let's make some iterations on the body of the, of the video.
Mm-Hmm. But we don't even test.
We don't, you're not even looking at
what percentage they even got 'em to,
to click through or even
Yeah. Not
click through, but look at the rest of the video
with thumb, thumb stoppers. Right?
Yeah. Does that make sense?
It makes perfect sense. Um,
So, so this year I think we're also what I said, you know,
well, I mean we all kind of agreed on like,
before we do any body change of the body, we gotta look at
what our front wrist is
because that's what's gonna prove whether
or not they're even looking through.
Why would we change the, the midsection
to the end section when the drop off?
They didn't even care about the beginning in,
in general. Right? Yeah.
That's it man. So it's a, it's a very, very valid point.
And I make that, I try to make that point as well.
'cause some clients will be, can we change the CTA?
And I'm like, why? You know, like, yeah. Doesn't matter.
Like, they're not even watching to the very end.
Um, so I think
that's an opportunity if you haven't already presented it
as like stick, put your foot down as like, this is,
we need this, you know, this is gonna make us better.
Um, it's gonna make us clear
and we're not gonna be wasting our time doing these like,
random things that aren't moving the needle.
Our job is to move the needle, move the business forward,
move the creative, move the messaging forward, um,
and optimize every single day.
You know, that saying of like 1% better every day?
That's what what doesn't get measured doesn't get improved.
Right? What gets measured gets improved.
If you're losing weight, you're trying to lose weight,
you're stepping on that scale every day, you know
that you're making progress.
Even if it goes up, at least you know,
you're going up now you gotta recalibrate.
Mm-Hmm. I think just, just
that overall analogy is something,
especially for like big teams.
Um, and it's funny to me
because like even the size of of Ipsy, it's like nobody not,
there's not one company who's doing it.
Perfect. Yeah. Like, it doesn't matter how big you are.
Like there's like inefficiencies in all,
in all organizations, big and small.
And, um, it's because the, the level of experience
and like knowledge in this world is just the very few
people have like done it all.
And so you're hiring people who are like,
say they're a creative strategist
or something like their social media managers, right?
But they've never, never ran ads before.
They don't know what a CPC is.
They don't know what these metrics are.
And then they're like,
and so yeah, those decisions become kind of like, yeah.
So I get it, but I think you're on the right track there.
I think you a very strong foundation
and like, you know, I think that's gonna move the needle
for the business and I think that's an opportunity for you.
Like, oh dude, Eric presented this,
like, this is getting so much better.
Like mm-Hmm. That's how we do it. So That's awesome.
Um, yeah.
Ethan, what's your, um, what's your take on everything?
Are you gonna be continuing this performance,
creative like direction?
Um, I'm not sure. I, I quite, I quite like it.
It is a bit more fulfilling when you,
'cause when you, when something does well, you know,
it's more down to you.
'cause with the editing it's kind of like, it could be,
well it's a little bit of you,
but then there's a lot of other factors that,
that play into it as well.
But I think, well my name isn't really, the name
of the business isn't really like everything.
Do you know what I mean? It's just more editing. So
What did you mean about that?
Well, 'cause the name's e-com editing. Ah.
And that's, so that's not everything.
But yeah, no, I do really like it.
And like I said, my business partner Finn, he,
he's quite, he's quite creative.
Um, and he's quite good at that.
And he, he seems to enjoy it as well.
So I would like to do it,
but I think the name's a little bit wrong.
What do you think
You call 'em Edits? No,
I mean, yeah. Name doesn't matter too much.
It'll be okay. Whatever you decide.
You can call it potato and people
be like, okay, what's potato?
This is sick. It's just, it's how you market it,
you know, like, and brand it.
Yeah, exactly. Um, that's just
Market it. Yep,
Yep, yep.
Um, yeah, dude, I mean,
there's a new company called Bad Marketing and,
but it's an acronym for like something I don't know.
But it, it's, it sounds like,
like it would be a terrible decision to call your,
your agency bad marketing, but, um,
Ugly ads.
Yeah. Ugly ads is a real thing, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I've seen that. Um, that's dope.
Um, so
before we kind of like wrap up,
is there any other like last things
that you guys are working on or need help with?
Um, personal business?
Uh, I have a question.
I've been seeing a lot of Ad Worlds Pro.
Have you like even done a seven day trial with them
or seen what they have?
So what it is, have you seen them? Mm-Hmm.
Yeah, for sure. So what's your thoughts on that?
Um, I haven't signed up for it myself. Mm-Hmm.
Um, I think there's a lot.
I think I was just kind of like
overwhelmed by like how much,
There's a lot, right?
Yeah. There's a lot going on in there.
Um, and I mean, it's
some of the best in the game for sure.
Right. Okay. Um, pick
and choose who you, who you wanna learn from.
Mm-Hmm. Really? I think it comes down to, um, there's a ton
of great people on here. Like people
There is a, the reason why I ask is
because, um,
they'll get a membership for the team. So I'm like,
Why Not? Is it a thing
that we should,
I'm not, it's not outta my pocket.
So I'm like, but is it worth it?
Or should I find another, um,
thing that can help with ads?
No, I think it's definitely worth it. Yeah.
Um, just because like, the quality
of the content is like very performance
driven type of stuff.
Um, like I've, I've bought a lot of the courses from some
of these people, like, okay, Molly Pittman, and,
and you know, like, um, I've seen Marella, uh,
Cress, krep Crespi.
She has a similar agency to me.
And she, like, one of her presentations was just like,
so good about like direct response, like UGC, like they,
they just focus on UGC.
And it was everything that like, I already knew,
but it's just like a, a new take.
Like everyone has a different spin on things, you know?
Um, so I think there's
a great opportunity to take courses, uh, in different,
um, what's it called?
Like different parts of the e-comm business.
Like people do landing pages and offers and media buying.
When you watch that, it only makes you as a creative better
because now your frame of reference is a lot larger.
Right. Like, it's only gonna
because you're making more connections.
That's the biggest thing.
And obviously I would do it all, just didn't have,
don't have the time to create it all.
But when, when you learn media buying,
when you learn offers, when you learn a landing page,
when you learn email, when you learn all that stuff,
it's like, dude, like, like the biggest takeaway for me is
because we start from the very beginning in the
funnel, from the creative.
How do I make creative congruent throughout the
entire brand, the entire funnel?
Make a creative that's so specific in messaging that
after they click, it's almost like they're in the perfect
place and the messaging is congruent from start to checkout.
And when you're able to keep
that messaging super clear, I think you've nailed it.
So you're gonna learn, you know, if you take any
of these other courses, you're gonna learn kind, kind
of like the nitty gritties of stuff.
But as a creative, like first that's your foundation
and then you're just layering in more Mm-Hmm.
Experience. So yeah, dude, I would love, yeah.
Do you share anything you find that's valuable?
I mean, it's badass. Cool man.
I'll do Alex for MO'S in there too. That's sick.
How'd you like that book? Have you read it?
Have you gone through it yet?
I read some of it. Um, did you
Get his first book?
A hundred million off? Yeah.
I like listening to some of it on, on,
on audio, audio podcast.
Um, I think the hardest part is, um, you know,
taking all the information then executing on it, right?
Like, yeah, okay, I learned this. Now what?
Like, that's the hardest part.
Implementation of
Implementation.
Yeah. Yeah. Um, are you,
are you working on anything yourself?
Have you thought about doing, going on, going solo?
Are you still building that course with your wife? We
We're, we're launching on the 22nd right now.
We just finished up our, our landing page, um,
our webinar deck, our training decks.
Um, now we're on a runway to start promoting it.
Like pre, you know, like planting seeds.
We built a, you know, we have an opt-in
or a freebie that will eventually
will go into promoting our training.
Amazing. Yeah. January 22nd. Excited about it.
I've doubt There's a lot of work, dude.
Yeah, it's definitely not easy,
but you're gonna learn a ton from doing it yourself.
We ran it once, three years ago. Okay.
Um, but then she got really backed up
with sponsors and all that stuff.
So she was focused on that.
Got, you know, her contracts then now
we're like, okay, I'm kind of slow.
It's so crazy that it, we're slow
and we're building the course, so worked out.
Oh, I know. In terms of busyness. Yeah.
You need that downtime.
Yeah, dude. Totally. Man.
Yeah, dude, just building, building the ads
or X course took me like a month.
Um, and I had to like, my business lost so much money.
My other, my other business
'cause I wasn't paying attention to it.
So it's like to build courses takes a lot
of time. Focus. Uh,
Bro, your ads are crazy.
Like, is that just one ad you're running?
Yeah. That ad we're gonna retire at soon.
Uh, I just shot a bunch of new ads.
A but yeah, that thing gained a ton of social proof
That the ads arex one.
Yeah, That, that always pops up on my phone,
dude. It like,
Why are you gonna retire?
Just lower budget on it, but, um, ah, okay. Okay. Yeah.
Just so the frequency doesn't, isn't so high.
'cause you know, when someone sees the same ad
over now, they're not buying from it. It's
Getting Yeah. It's skinny.
Yeah. It's losing. Um, I'm, I'm sorry,
Go ahead bro. I've got, I've
got a question for you.
Um, it's, it's not really on topic. Well it is on topic.
It's about personal task management
and like any routines that you feel have helped you.
Because what I kind of find myself doing is just 24 7,
just kind of wake up, working, go to sleep, wake up working.
I didn't know if you kind of at a set time you stop work
or you have a routine, like you go
to the gym every time at this morning or, and,
and like how you assign tasks as well.
'cause I have like five different notebooks
and I use like, notes on my computer.
Mm-Hmm. And, and then there's other things.
And so outta them two things, like routines
and kind of keeping your day on track.
Mm-Hmm. Because, well, also
what I do is I time block my day out.
Mm-Hmm. And it never goes on plan at all. And
Sorry, it's funny. Yeah.
Totally relatable. So
How do you, how have you kind
of overcome both of them things?
What do you like religiously do
or what do you find has really helped you
Love that question.
You know, it took a lot, took a lot of time to get
to a place where I could find consistency
in my life.
Um, so obviously you don't have kids, which is nice.
But on the downside, because
before I had kids I was like even more of a workaholic.
And I would, I, I I'd work, I could work four, eight hours
and just grind through it
and like then suffer for like a day
and a half, you know, two days to make up for it.
Um, I think
work is always gonna be there, right?
There's always gonna be requests,
there's always gonna be things to execute on.
There's always gonna be things to fulfill.
There's always gonna be fires to put out.
And, um, you have to start setting limitations to yourself,
your energy and your focus.
And you have to set time.
Like be much more intentional with your time.
Um, so for me, because I'll share one quick story.
'cause yesterday I looked at my phone
and I don't know if you have slack and all these things.
I was like, I told my wife, I was like, I have
so many people to get back to right now.
And you know, if you're not in control of this,
like you can start to feel like the, like you're tensing up.
Like you can feel like the anxiety, you can feel the stress
and you're like, oh, I need to just do this right now.
But you're what you're not,
what you're not doing is creating boundaries for yourself
and for the people that you're working with.
And so when you just become,
when you don't create boundaries for yourself,
then you just allow other people to kind
of like access you at any time, right?
Um, so I've had to learn that
and my wife's like, just get back
to them in the morning, you know?
And I was like, okay, then it's like one less thing I have
to worry about and I could
sleep peacefully and all this stuff.
So anyways, I think I already told Eric this,
but I wake up at 4:00 AM every day
because I prefer the peace
and quiet in the morning versus pushing my body late at
night to get something done.
Because that is also a disservice to yourself
and your health, uh, because you're running on fumes
and you're running, you're,
you're burning the midnight oil, right?
You're burning the candle from both ends.
You're not gonna get your best work in when you're pushing
your body to its limit.
And it's, and your mental health is gonna suffer as well.
Um, so just like you, like I do have time blocks,
but they're, they're focused around my children.
Um, but in place of that, for example, instead of like,
you know, I've to take my kids to school, I have
to make a lunch, I have to do all that stuff.
That becomes your time to prioritize yourself
and your health, which is working out
for 30 minutes reading.
So actually before I even start work,
because it is, is not good to go from bed to like,
all right, let me just get all these,
see these messages and start reacting.
Dude, your cortisol levels, your stress,
your anxiety is gonna go.
Um, and that's not a good way to start your day.
'cause then the rest of your day is gonna be like
that very reactive.
And, um, I hate that feeling.
So I don't know if you meditate
or you do anything like to give yourself some space,
um, chill out.
But I do, I do meditation every morning. 15, 15, 30 minutes.
I set intentions for the day.
Like, it's very important that you quiet your mind
before you get into your work.
So you come to this place of like, equanimity,
peace, like centeredness.
Because if you allow those thoughts to kind of like,
you know, because all these things are
gonna come at you, right?
And if you, if you go to this side
or go to that, like you're, you're just teeter tottering.
You're focused back and forth
versus coming to a place of center.
And so you need to do that just like you were
to like brush your teeth.
It's like getting centered I think is one of the key things
to having a really productive day.
So set time, whatever that is for you, doing a walk,
you know, listening to music, meditating, praying, um,
you know, whatever piece you find.
And then I think from there it's like, I like to,
because I'm like, okay, I'm gonna block out two hours
or an hour and a half to try to get some
of the hardest stuff done.
The stuff that's like top of my plate
and then I'm gonna step away and take a break.
Like, 'cause it's easy
to just get lost in the sauce there and then keep going.
Um, so I'm actually forced to take a break
'cause I got 7:00 AM I have to get kids ready.
So that could be an opportunity for you to be like,
all right, I'm gonna go do something for me.
I'm gonna go work out. I'm gonna go, you know, read,
I'm gonna do something, I'm gonna take a break
and then come back
and then do another time block, eat a lunch,
and then do another time block.
And then at a certain time you have to cut off work.
Like there's no if ands or buts
because that you have to give your body enough time
to like settle down and to be, get on a sleep routine.
I think if you don't have a sleep routine in place,
you are also like hurting yourself physically and mentally.
Um, I've interviewed like 10 sleep experts just
'cause um, and they're like, you know,
that circadian rhythm man, like you have to have your own
kind of process of winding down.
No phones, like tv, that kind of stuff.
I know it's, I mean, we all do it to some degree, right?
But I find myself like falling asleep at like 8 30, 9,
9:00 PM every single day because my body's now on a clock.
And dude, trust me, this took me so many years to get to.
I'm not saying it's you should do it.
It's like that's, it's what the consequence
of like waking up at the same time every day
and going to sleep at the same time every day ends up being,
and you have this consistent energy throughout the day.
You're not like one day super tired
and then like next day you're super jacked
because you got extra sleep and it's like this up and down.
I hate that. That's like what I lived through for years.
Um, so there's a discipline involved setting times
of waking up and then setting times of going to bed
and like cutting off work
and then creating space for yourself within that time.
Um, just so you feel like fulfilled in other things too.
You know, it's not always about work.
Um, as much as we wanna work and we want to please people
and we wanna make, you know, make money and all that stuff.
Like if you're not filling up your own
tank, you'd have nothing to give.
You know, if, like for me, sometimes it's like listening
to old punk rock, like old pop punk music
and just like walking my dogs and like, I'm stoked.
Like I wrote a song the other day, like,
I haven't written music in so long and I wrote a song
and I recorded it and I was like, dude,
this is so, oh my God.
It was so nice to create something that had no agenda
and no expectation.
You know what I mean? Like,
I don't know what it is for you guys.
I'm sure you guys are artists or creative in some way too.
Like, you know, you didn't just,
you didn't start editing videos, ads when you're like one.
Um, but yeah. Is that helpful, Ethan?
I'm just kind of breaking it
Down. Yeah, that's, that is very helpful.
That is very helpful.
I, yeah, that was a lot of great advice in there.
I think for the, also for the sleep routines,
something I've found recently is, have you heard
of blue light blockers?
Yeah. Yeah. I've, I've, so I've got some like glasses.
Nice. And I've got like orange, orange tints on them
and they help because all the blue light from your phone to
and like screens tells your brain
that it's awake 'cause Mm-Hmm.
I used to find myself struggling to get to sleep just
because like you've got a big monitor in front of you
and then you just go into the bed the next minute
and so that, that's helped.
But yeah, I definitely agree.
I think, 'cause at the moment I'm quite sporadic
with like wake up and bedtimes.
Mm-Hmm. I, I, so yeah, that is good
that I do really like that.
Do you have on the weekends as well, do you kind of stop
or is take like Sunday for rest?
Yeah, I think it's really important
and I've, I've talked to a PhD on sleep
and he's like waking up at the same time no matter what.
Um, even on the weekends, like
however on Sundays, like I'll still wake up,
but I'm not really like really grinding, you know?
Um, so I do take one day off to like recharge.
You need that, definitely need that.
But it's also, and this is something I'm still working on,
is like on the weekends, like I'll goof
around a little bit in terms of like my diet.
Like I'll kind of like, I'll be lazier than
like the average day.
And that kind of eats at me on Mondays.
So it's like, oh, now it's like really hard
to get back into the flow and the swing of things.
Um, so I think keeping that consistency is important.
But you, yeah, resting, like doing nothing is very helpful,
you know, that doesn't mean like sitting around
and watching Netflix all day as much as I like doing that.
Um, but it's like doing something else, like going outside,
like going on an adventure, planning a trip, you know,
really nature, like going out, seeing nature.
Like, gosh, I'm like just seeing out,
going outside for a second.
I'm like, dude, God, it feels
so much better out here than it does in my office.
Like, you know, we need that sun.
I mean, you're in the uk I
don't know how much sun you get, but,
Um, not, not much at all.
My, my car was completely frozen this morning.
Oh, snap. And there, there's no sun at all. No.
Well, there is a little bit, but it's very dark
and rainy and cold.
Um, I hope you're staying happy in other ways, man.
Some of the nature is quite nice.
There's quite a lot of like trees
and fields like where I live, which is nice.
But, uh, uh, it is,
the weather is quite miserable a lot of the time.
I love how straightforward it is about it.
Um, Eric, is there anything you wanna add to that?
Um, dude, time blocking.
I actually, I actually time block on my Google calendar.
Hmm. So when I have, I break it down like
first four hours is for myself
and then the, the next four hours or eight hours is for Ipsy
and then the next four hours
after that will be, um, family time.
Like dinner. I can pull it up.
I don't know if I could share screen. Lemme see.
I'm breaking down how it looks. Lemme see, lemme check.
Yeah, a hundred percent. Can you see
It? Yeah,
I pulled it up.
Um, so like the first four hours of working, walk
and pray, that's what you're talking about.
Meditation. Yes. And having my breakfast,
everything's locked, kinda locked in.
Love it. So that I'm systematized and then my workflow
and then kids down here, like my daughter and family, oops.
Is all that love. Um, that's it,
Man. I had, I had
to have, I had to ha I had to do it this way
because if I didn't, um, I'd be all over the place.
Sometimes there's little things that, that we'll get in.
Like today I didn't have this scheduled,
but I know that I have a block from Right. 10 to 11.
Right. But everything's blocked out for me every day.
And then talking about Sabbath, I do Sabbath, um,
whether it's Saturday or Sunday.
Yeah. Like, like this too. Yeah. So if, yeah. Right.
If you went to, what is that?
What do you, what, what would it look like on
a weekly view even, right? It would be like that.
Yeah. This is, yeah, it's pretty much pretty consistent.
But like, I have all the things like broke, broken down,
but these white parts are like,
oh, I have some breaks there.
I know I can, but all the grayed out stuff is like,
we're nope, we're done. Yeah.
And it, like, that's a big thing I did, I had to, to do
was cut off work.
Mm-Hmm. Especially Ethan, you don't have a family
so you can just grind all, you know, grind all day.
Right. You don't have kids and a wife.
I don't know if you have wife or,
but um, you can just go at it, but you need it.
There must be a time where you're,
where there's a cutoff, cutoff time. Absolutely.
I've, I've, yeah, I I I agree with all of that.
Both of you got some really good points. I, I think so.
Cutoff time is definitely needed.
'cause I don't, I don't do that at the moment.
And, and what I,
what John also you said about running on the midnight oil
and, and I, I noticed that at night
and time you just, you'll, you'll be sitting there working
and just, nothing's really, nothing's really happening.
And yeah, thank you both
Of Yeah, I've been there, bro.
Ethan, when I was at your age,
I wish I time blocked everything
because I was just going at it.
Um, overnighters. Mm-Hmm. Um, just grinding, right?
And then learning how to do this.
But you need the rest and,
and time for yourself, like what John was saying,
like meditating or, you know, walking,
that starts off the day, right?
Yeah. Instead of just going into,
all right, let me start working. Mm-Hmm.
Yeah. It's the pre it's the pre-workout,
you know, it's the pre that's
The pre-workout.
Yeah. You gotta pre blah, blah, blah yourself
before you get into something
or like it's a warmup, you know, you gotta warm yourself up.
You gotta get in tune with yourself.
'cause when you're sleeping, you know, like you're just,
you have to do a reset every morning.
You have to do a reset every morning.
Like you have to get, like Eric's is walk and pray.
Like, I, I found this out
through like hitting my head against the wall.
It's like there's no other way
to like jump in there without,
by being like the most productive without setting
those standards for myself.
You know? And even like, I don't, like, I don't even get
to shower every morning, but like, I should include
that more often in my schedule.
But like, I I, it's like, it's like these non-negotiables
that you create for yourself there
It is. Non-negotiables.
Yeah. That's what you need for yourself
and it's different for everyone.
But I think that you will find that.
And when you do let us know.
'cause we'll be rooting for you.
Thank you. Amazing guys. Thanks guys.
Well that was a phone call. Thanks for jumping on. Both you.
It's always good to connect with you guys
and, um, just catch up on everything.
So, um, I guess we'll talk to you guys soon
and, uh, Ethan, keep me posted on the other stuff.
Yeah, sure. What, what do you want?
Just more results if they come through.
Yeah. Anything that comes in.
But, um, I'll share kinda my updates on my end
as well. Okay.
Quick question, John, you had a, um, someone
that did a live with you, um, I forget his name.
Mm-Hmm. That talks about framework?
Yeah. Is it on Slack? Like did you record it?
Yeah, we recorded it. We'll post it soon.
Oh, okay. It's gonna be posted soon. All right.
I was just wondering if you were gonna share that out.
Yeah, no worries. Definitely will.
Um, yeah, Billy bro. Billy
Broz. There
You go. He's a boss.
Thank you. All right guys.
I'll talk to you soon. Have a good rest of your day.
Thank you, you too. Cheers Guys. Thanks guys.